Class of 1916 Records 1912-1996
Smith College Archives
Class of 1916 Records
1912-1996
Smith College. Class of 1916.
RG 80 UUID:2fa648fa-e866-4097-b823-14c55cc981a0
24 boxes (20 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 24 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1916.
The Class of 1916 was the thirty-seventh entering class and the thirty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1916 records, 1912-1996, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1916, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1916 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 1)
- Book of Statistics 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 3)
- Commencement Clippings 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 5)
- Commencement Photos 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 6)
- Commencement Speaker 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 7)
- Freshman Frolic 1912 (Box 1882, Folder 8)
- Freshman Grind 1912 (Box 1882, Folder 9)
- Freshman Handbook 1912-1913 (Box 1882, Folder 10)
- Groups 1912-1916 (Box 1882, Folder 11)
- Hoop Rolling 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day Photos 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 14)
- Junior Frolic 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 15)
- Junior Prom 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 16)
- Junior Prom: Garden Party 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 17)
- Junior Ushers 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 18)
- Last Chapel 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 1)
- Class Letters 1916-1970 (Box 1883, Folder 2)
- Class Letters 1970-1980 (Box 1883, Folder 3)
- Organization 1915-1916 (Box 1883, Folder 4)
- Step Sings 1915-1916 (Box 1883, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 6)
- Senior Dramatics: Photos 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 7)
- Senior Dramatics: Photo Album 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 8)
- Senior Reception 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 9)
- Smock Day 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 10)
- Songs undated (Box 1883, Folder 11)
- Sophomore Reception 1913 (Box 1883, Folder 12)
- Class Supper 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 13)
- Reunions-General 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1917-1919 (Box 1884, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1921 (Box 1884, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1926 (Box 1884, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1931 (Box 1884, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1936 (Box 1884, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 7)
- Reunions-Photographs 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 8)
- Reunions-Photographs 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1946 (Box 1884, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1951 (Box 1884, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1956 (Box 1884, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1961 (Box 1884, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 1884, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 1884, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 1884, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1975-1976 (Box 1884, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1981 (Box 1884, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1986 (Box 1884, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1991-1992 (Box 1884, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1996 (Box 1884, Folder 21)
- Reunions undated (Box 1884, Folder 22)
- Reunions-Songs undated (Box 1884, Folder 23)